contentforest.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy | ContentForest

## **Privacy policy**

88Projects Limited **("We")** are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our **Terms and Conditions** and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting contentforest.com and all included sub-pages **("Site")** you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

#### Information you give us

You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our Site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our Site, subscribe to our service, and when you report a problem with our Site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number.

#### Information we collect about you

With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:

  * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time); page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, mouse-overs and search queries), and methods used to browse away from the page.

#### Information we receive from other sources

We may receive information about you if you use any of the other Sites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site. Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Site or by the owners of third party services used by this Site, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features may be disabled, and failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Site to provide its services.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

#### Information you give us

We will use this information:

  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information and services that you request from us;
  * to provide you with information about other services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
  * to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about your search queries, goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * to ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

#### Information we collect about you

We will use this information:

  * to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, database extension, statistical and survey purposes;
  * to improve our Site and database to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so, and to present you with the service you request;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure;
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
  * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
  * to keep track of search and usage behavior

#### Information we receive from other sources

We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

### Disclosure of your information

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Site.
  * Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * if 88Projects Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our **Terms and Conditions** and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of 88Projects Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, processed and stored at, a destination in the United States and New Zealand. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will process and store your information in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized access.

Your information processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to us, in some cases, your information may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the Site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies).

Your information is processed at the 88Project’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact **support@contentforest.com**.

### Your rights

Your information is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by you, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and you can always request that your information is suspend or remove.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing and database extension purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for marketing purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at **support@contentforest.com**.

You have the right, at any time, to know whether your personal data has been stored and can consult us to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to **support@contentforest.com**.

This Site does not support “Do Not Track” requests.

To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the Sites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these Sites, please note that these Sites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these Sites.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to **support@contentforest.com**.

88Projects Limited

Last updated: May 2016
